feedseva.com 2014-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore

## 

##  Privacy Policy

The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore shares your concerns about privacy on the Internet. In order to better protect your privacy, We have provided this notice explaining its online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on the Site. Furthermore, this _Privacy_ _Policy_ , being part of the Terms, works in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions of Use, but does not modify or supercede it. On occasion, The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore may run promotions or conduct other activities with affiliate partners from this Site. In such event, we may post additional privacy terms in conjunction with such promotion or activities that modify and/or supplement this _Privacy Policy_ and govern the use of information related to or received through such promotions or activities.

**The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginiaand the Eastern Shore's Collection and Use of Your** **Information  
**    
In the course of using the Site, The Foodbank may ask you for your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, fax number as well as other relevant information. The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Google Chrome, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon FIOS, AOL, COX), aggregate data about the number of visits to the Site and/or aggregate data about the pages visited.

**How The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia Uses the Information** The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore uses the non-personally identifiable information ("Aggregate Data") to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable The Foodbank to personalize your Internet experience. The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore may use the Aggregate Data to analyze Site usage as well as create services and/or products to fit your needs. Also, The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore shares this Aggregate Data with The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore's related entities, advertisers, partners and/or other third party vendors. The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore shall own such Aggregate Data and maintain copies of such as part of its records.

**_Except as otherwise indicated_ **, The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore uses the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you provide about yourself: (a) to respond to any of your inquiries or questions about our services; (b) for internal marketing purposes and as part of The Foodbank's donor database; (c) to provide you additional and updated information, materials and other advertisements regarding the The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore's services; (d) to offer you other materials and/or information that The Foodbank believes may be of interest to you; (e) to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law, or as otherwise required by law; (f) to protect the security or integrity of the Site; (g) to protect against a threat of safety or destruction of property; and/or (h) to protect against legal liability.

**_In all cases_ **, however, The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore agents, employees and contractors who have access to Personal Information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this _Privacy Policy_. Furthermore, The Foodbank encourages all its business Partners to adopt and adhere to standards of protection consistent with this _Privacy Policy_. The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore will not use the Personal Information, except as set forth herein, without your permission; provided, however, The Foodbank shall own all such Personal Information and maintain copies of such as part of its records. If you do not wish to receive any such information or to allow The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore the right to use your personally identifiable information as described, [_please contact The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore_](mailto:digitalmedia@foodbankonline.org?subject=OPT%20OUT%20-%20ONLINE)  in the manner identified in the "Opt-Out" section below. The Aggregate Data and Personal Information may be transferred, distributed or sold as part of The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore or its assets.

**Opt Out** You may choose not to receive such information and/or to allow The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore to use your information in the manner described above by simply checking the box provided on the contribution form itself, or by contacting us directly at [_digitalmedia@foodbankonline.org_](mailto:digitalmedia@foodbankonline.org). Upon receipt and processing of an "opt out" request, The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore will, within its commercially reasonable amount of time, remove your information from any future marketing communications.

**Security; No Liability  
**   
The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and teh Eastern Shore has implemented security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse and alteration of any information under The Foodbank's control. The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore protects your online order information by using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. SSL encrypts your order information to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore. Nevertheless, such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information on the Site, and The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore is not responsible for any damages or liabilities relating to any such security failures. You understand that data and communications, including e-mail and other electronic communications, may be accessed by unauthorized third parties when communicated over the Internet. Furthermore, the Site contains links to other web sites. The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore is not responsible for nor can The Foodbank ensure the privacy practices or content of such other sites.

**IP Addresses and Cookies  
**    
Like other web sites, The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore's servers, to administer the Site and for security purposes.   
"Cookies" are pieces of data sent from a web server to a web browser that enable a web server to identify users that visit a site hosted by that server. The Foodbank may use Cookies in order to identify you to our site so that The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore can provide more customized information and services to you. In addition, our site may contain advertisements that may contain Cookies. In general, if you choose, you can disable the use of Cookies by reviewing your browser's preferences and options.

**A Special Note about Children**

 The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore does not knowingly gather any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.  You must be 13 years of age or older to access the Site.  The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore has no interest in collecting information from children under the age of 13.

**Modification of Privacy Policy  
**    
The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore may change this Privacy Policy at any time, consistent with the terms set forth in the Terms and Conditions of Use, by posting the changed or amended Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued viewing of or use of this Site following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to any such changes or amendments.

**How to Contact The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore for Any Reason  
**    
You may contact The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, updating any personally identifiable information or anything else related to The Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia and the Eastern Shore and/or this Site via _ **email**_ at [_digitalmedia@foodbankonline.org_](mailto:digitalmedia@foodbankonline.org) or by **_calling_** 757-627-6599.

  ** _Updated October 4, 2013_**
